anyone who is given the job,
the duty, in any form in this
ummah
no matter the job,
you are given the job of an
imam in your masjid
you are given the job of a
principal in your school
headmaster in your school
you are given the job of a
head of department
you are the head of the law
chamber
you are the head,
the clinical head
or the head of department in
the
hospital
or the dean of the faculty
anybody who is placed in
charge of
anything
he has been given any
particular job
in the affairs of this ummah
and then he takes it easy
with
the people
he makes life easy for them
he supports them
he helps them
he overlooks their faults
he makes things easy for them
this kind of a person,
be easy with him
look at this dua
anyone placed in charge of
anything in
this ummah
and then he is easy
he is nice to them
he rules them well
he is fair to them
be easy with him
be kind towards him
O Allah show your favors on
him